DESMOND ANTROBUS

• DETAILS •

(647)-289-2123 desmond.antrobus@live.ca

SKILLS

Active Listening

Customer Service

Fast Learner

Computer Skills

Teamwork

Ability to Multitask

Communication Skills

PROFILE

My experience in the service industry and warehouse operation has helped me hone my communication and customer service skills. With an amiable and diligent outlook, a contact center representative role would be an ideal step to focus the next chapter of my career.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Parts Handler at Altrom Auto Group, Scarborough

September 2014 — Present

- Performed related duties including unloading shipments, receiving and inventory
- Provide customers with quick and accurate service at pick up counter
- Receive payment for goods and process cash and credit/debit card payments
- Applied knowledge of products to help ensure customers orders are correct
- · Help other departments as needed
- · Revise stock order to correct any stock discrepancies

Bar Back at Cake Bar & Night Club, Toronto

September 2017 — March 2019

- Greeted bottle service guests by escorting them to assigned booth
- Ensured bottle service guests had clean cups and mixes
- Consistently collect, wash, sanitize and restock all glass and bar-ware for repeated bartender use
- · Assisted with bottle service setup and bussing
- Perform general duties such as taking out trash, stocking restrooms, and complying with special requests set forth by management.

EDUCATION

High School Diploma, St. John Paul II Catholic Secondary School, Scarborough September 2008 — June 2011

¶ REFERENCES

• References available upon request